Disaster is just a small step away.
Mr. Bean's Holiday is a family, comedy film directed by Steve Bendelack.
Bean wins a trip to Cannes where he unwittingly separates a young
boy from his father and must help the two reunite.
On the way he discovers France, bicycling and true love, among other things.
Mr. Bean, played by Rowan Atkinson.
Carson Clay, played by Willem Dafoe.
Stepan, played by Maxim Baldry.
Emil, played by Karel Roden.
Sabine, played by Emma de Caunes.
Vicar, played by Steve Pemberton.
Bean's Holiday is a 2007 British comedy film directed by Steve
Bendelack and written by Hamish McColl and Robin Driscoll.
Based on the British sitcom series Mr.
Bean created by Rowan Atkinson and Richard
Curtis, it is a sequel to Bean (1997).
The film stars Atkinson as Mr.
Bean, with Maxim Baldry, Emma de Caunes, Willem Dafoe
and Karel Roden in supporting roles.
In the film, Mr.
Bean wins a trip to Cannes, France, but on his way there, he is mistaken for a kidnapper and meets an
award-winning filmmaker after he travels with both a Russian filmmaker's son and an aspiring actress in tow.
The film premiered on 25 March 2007 at the Odeon Leicester Square in London, and was
theatrically released in the United Kingdom on 30 March 2007 by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics, and was a box-office success,
grossing $232 million against a budget of $25 million.
The film explores themes of france, movie business,
language barrier, clumsy fellow, to drop brick.
The tone is lighthearted.